Predrag Markovic

Profile

Many years of experience as Software developer including working with different programming languages and platforms.

Connecting sports with IT through the presentation of statistics and sport events in mobile application and website.

Experience working with posters and presentations

Education

Software Engineering - Metropolitan, University of Information Technology

Nis, Serbia 2020 - Present

C#, Java, PHP Developer - IT Academy

Belgrade, Serbia 2011 - 2013

Book accountant - Higher Business School of Professional Studies

Leskovac, Serbia 2003 – 2005

Employment History

Mobile developer, Totalview department, Formula

www.formula.fo, www.total-view.com

Torshavn, Faroe Islands, February 2014 – Present

Owner and (Xamarin, Net Maui and Web) developer Dystir.fo

Website: www.dystir.fo

Torshavn, Faroe Islands, 2019 - Present

Programming Languages and Platforms

Java Android, Kotlin

Application: Totalview

https://play.google.com/store/search?q=totalview&c=apps

demo server: demo.totalview.cloud

login: tt/Password0 2015 – Present

Objective C, Swift

Application: Totalview

https://apps.apple.com/dk/app/totalview/id668350774?l=en

demo server: demo.totalview.cloud

login: tt/Password0 2018 – Present

Xamarin, Net Maui

Applications: Dystir, DystirManager

Android: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=fo.Dystir iOS: https://apps.apple.com/dk/app/dystir/id1460781430?l=en

2019 – Present

C#, Blazor, React, JavaScript, Html, CSS

Website: www.dystir.fo

2019 - Present



INFO

ADDRESS

Vognmansmarken 4, 1. tv, Roskilde 4000 Denmark

PHONE

004542703679

EMAIL

predragmarkovic77@hotmail.com

LANGUAGES

CROATIAN	

ENGLISH		
DANISH		_

SKILLS IN PROGRAMMING

υП			
		_	

Xamarin, Net Maui

Objective C

Swift

Java, Kotlin

Blazor, React

JavaScript, jQuery

Html, CSS